Guide to the Stanford Unviersity, Hispanic American Institute, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Unviersity, Hispanic American Institute, records
1949-1965
SC0075
Stanford University. Hispanic American Institute.
1 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Correspondence.; Hispanic Americans; Stanford University--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Records, 1949-1965
  - Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1964 Jan-Apr (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1964 May-Sep (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1964 Oct-Nov (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Dec, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1965 Jan-Feb (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1965 Mar-May (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1965 Jun-Dec (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1961 Apr-1965 Sep (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Supporting material, 1948-1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Supporting material, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Supporting material, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)